popeyescanada.com 2018-09-04

# Popeye's Supplements Canada ~ Over 140 Locations Across Canada! - Privacy Statement

> ## PRIVACY STATEMENT
> 
> PopeyesCanada.com is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the PopeyesCanada.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the PopeyesCanada.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 
> 
> **Please note that this Web site is intended for use only by residents of Canada.**
> 
> **Collection of your Personal Information**  
>  PopeyesCanada.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. PopeyesCanada.com also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
> 
> There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by PopeyesCanada.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by PopeyesCanada.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PopeyesCanada.com Web site.
> 
> Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through PopeyesCanada.com public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: PopeyesCanada.com does not read any of your private online communications.
> 
> **Use of your Personal Information**  
>  PopeyesCanada.com collects and uses your personal information to operate the PopeyesCanada.com Web site and deliver the services you have requested. PopeyesCanada.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PopeyesCanada.com and its affiliates. PopeyesCanada.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
> 
> PopeyesCanada.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. PopeyesCanada.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, PopeyesCanada.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to PopeyesCanada.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
> 
> PopeyesCanada.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
> 
> PopeyesCanada.com keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within PopeyesCanada.com, in order to determine what PopeyesCanada.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within PopeyesCanada.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
> 
> PopeyesCanada.com Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PopeyesCanada.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PopeyesCanada.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PopeyesCanada.com, or the public.
> 
> **Security of your Personal Information**  
>  PopeyesCanada.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. PopeyesCanada.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
> 
> **Changes to this Statement**  
>  PopeyesCanada.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. PopeyesCanada.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how PopeyesCanada.com is protecting your information.
> 
> **Contact Information**  
>  PopeyesCanada.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that PopeyesCanada.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact PopeyesCanada.com at:
> 
>   
> 
> 
> **PopeyesCanada.com**  
>  c/o Popeye's Supplements Canada Inc.  
>  #100, 10327 - 178 Street  
>  Edmonton, AB T5S 1R5
> 
> We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
